Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 63, folder: 25 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 32: Lay-Off Allowance Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 33: Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 34: Qualification Record, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 35: An Idea with a Future, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 36: Ph. D. Application for Employment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 37: Your Future with Haynes Stellite, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 38: Our Three-Minute StoryYour Career With Union Carbide Metals, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 39: Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 40: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 41: At Career for youat Union Carbide's General Offices, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 42: The Pension Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 43: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 44: Information for Employees in the New York General Offices, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 45: Savings Plan for Employees, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 46: Major Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 47: An Idea With A Future, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 48: 3 Minutes on Your Future With Carbide, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 49: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 50: Union Carbide in Nuclear Energy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 51: Ph. D. Application for Employment, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 52: A Career in Plastics, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Item 53: The PhD at Union Carbide, Publication (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Box: 63, folder: 26 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Matching Grant Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 26)
- Box: 63, folder: 27 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Accounting Opportunities, Publication (Box 63, Folder 27)
- Box: 63, folder: 28 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: 1974 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Employee Training: How Union Electric Developed It's "Safety in the Home" Program, Publication (Box 63, Folder 28)
- Box: 63, folder: 29 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Union Electric: Growingsince 1902, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Taum Sauk: Union Electric's Pumped Storage Hydro Plant, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Careersfor high school graduates, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: History of Union Electric Company, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Engineering: St. Louis, Missouri, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Standard Safe Working Practices and Procedures for Union Electric Employes, Publication (Box 63, Folder 29)
- Box: 63, folder: 30 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: 1970 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: 1964 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: 1966 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: 1968 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Metropolitant St. Louis, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: 1969 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: 1971 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: Report to Stockholders First Quarter 1971, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Report to Stockholders First Quarter 1969, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Report to Stockholders First Quarter 1972, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Report to Stockholders Second Quarter 1970, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: Report to Stockholders Second Quarter 1969, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: Report to Stockholders Second Quarter 1971, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: Report to Stockholders Third Quarter 1971, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Report to Stockholders Third Quarter 1970, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: Report to Stockholders Third Quarter 1968, Publication (Box 63, Folder 30)
- Box: 63, folder: 31 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: 2nd Quarter Report 1973, Publication (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Board of Directors Adopts Statement of Policy on Conflict of Interest, Publication (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Item 3: New Safety Award Program Recognizes Wife's Vital Role in Preventing Employe Accidents, Publication (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Item 4: 1972 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Item 5: 1973 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 31)
- Box: 63, folder: 32 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: No Door Swings on One Hinge, Publication (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Union Oil Company Headquarters, Publication (Box 63, Folder 32)
- Box: 63, folder: 33 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    July-August 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    September 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: This is a "J" for Jobs Project Financed byUllico, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 4: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    November 1977. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    February 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 11: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 12: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 13: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    June-July 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 15: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 16: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 17: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    September 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 19: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 20: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 21: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 22: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 23: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    January-February 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
    January-Febraury 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: This is "J for Jobs" Project Financed byUllico, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 26: This is "J for Jobs" Project Financed byUllico, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 27: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 28: Ullico Bulletin, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Item 29: 1970 Annual Report, Publication (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Box: 63, folder: 34 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Working at Union Oil Center, Publication (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Working Together: A Handbook for Employees, Publication (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Reference Verification, Publication (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Sick Pay Allowance Policy, Publication (Box 63, Folder 34)
- Box: 63, folder: 35 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Management Organization, Publication (Box 63, Folder 35)
    September 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: A Series of Institutional Advertisements Explaining How and Why Amican Business Functions: 10th Edition, Publication (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: How to Work with the Press, Publication (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Box: 63, folder: 36 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The People Business, Publication (Box 63, Folder 36)
- Box: 64, folder: 1 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Promulgation of Revisions in Work Rules, Publication (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Box: 64, folder: 2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Rules, Publication (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Box: 64, folder: 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Union Square and You: Union Square Savings Bank Staff Handbook, Publication (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Box: 64, folder: 4 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Letter of Understanding by and between Union Tool Company and United Electrical, Publication (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Box: 64, folder: 5 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Dun's Review, Publication (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Box: 64, folder: 6 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Unitcast, Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Welcome American Society for Metals to Unitcast Corp., Publication (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Box: 64, folder: 7 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The United Aircraft Story, Publication (Box 64, Folder 7)
    By H. M. Horner. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 8 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1970, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1969, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1967, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1966, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1965, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1964, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: United Aircraft Corporation Pictorial Report 1954, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: United Aircraft Corporation Pictorial Report 1952, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: United Aircraft Corporation Pictorial Report 1955, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: United Aircraft Corporation Pictorial Report 1958, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: United Aircraft Pictorial Report 1962, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Bee-Hive Quarterly Publication of United Aircraft, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
    Fall 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Power Plant, Publication (Box 64, Folder 8)
    February 8, 1974. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 9 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Fingerprint Identification, Publication (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: United Aircraft Corporation Pictorial Report 1959, Publication (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: United Aircraft Retirement-Income Plans, Publication (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Certificate of Insurance: Group Health and Life Insurance Plan, Hourly Employees, Publication (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Certificate of Insurance: Group Health and Life Insurance Plan, Salary Employees, Publication (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Box: 64, folder: 10 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Joint Statement on "Plan for Progress", Publication (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Box: 64, folder: 11 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Here's a wonderful career opportunityFlight Officer with United Air Lines, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: You and United Air Lines, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: It Can Be Yours - A Career in the Skyas a United Airlines Stewardess, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Your Job Opportunity with United Airlines, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Your Future in Air Transportation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: A Reminder for Supervisors, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: The Mainliner Stewardess, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Your United Airllines Retirement Program, Publication (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Box: 64, folder: 12 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Condensed Version of the Railway Labor Act, Publication (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Findings Upon Investigation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 12)
    January 17, 1961. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Brief on Behalf of Flight Engineers' International Association, Publication (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Box: 64, folder: 13 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: United Air Lines Employees' Suggestion Conference: Its purpose and how it works, Publication (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Box: 64, folder: 14 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
    June 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United Air Lines News, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: United Air Lines News, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The Main Line: The Story of United Air Lines, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Wings of Progress: The First Quarter-Century of United Air Lines and Commercial Air Transport, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
    December 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: United Air Lines Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: News Bureau: United Air Lines, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: News Clippings, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: United Airlines Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: United Air Lines Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: United Air Lines Annual Report 1958, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: United Air Lines Annual Report 1959, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Twenty-First Edition Facts & Figures About Air Transportation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 16: Air Transportation: Facts and Figures, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 17: United Air Lines Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Item 18: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Box: 64, folder: 15 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: United Air Lines Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: United Air Lines Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Mainline Management Memo, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Mainline Management, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Mainline Management Memo, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Mainline Management Memo, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: United Mainliner Special Issue, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
    November 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
    August 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
    July 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
    March 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 15: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Item 16: Inside United, Publication (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Box: 64, folder: 16 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Collective Agreement between the United Association of Dress Manufacturers, Inc. and the National Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc., Publication (Box 64, Folder 16)
    December 2, 1933. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 17 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Annual Report for the Year Ended December 31, 1950, Publication (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Box: 64, folder: 18 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: United Fruit Company Operating Organization, Publication (Box 64, Folder 18)
    May 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: United Fruit Company Organization, Publication (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Box: 64, folder: 19 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Unifruitco, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
    April 29, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Tropical Radio Telegraph Company: Suggestion Program for Domestic Employees, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Tropical Radio Telegraph Company: Suggestion Program for Tropical Employees, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Unifruitco (in Spanish), Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
    November-December 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Unifruitco, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 6: The Story of the Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Pan American School of Agriculture), Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 7: Unifruitco, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
    March-April 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: U.F. Report, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 9: How an American Company, Through Advertising and Public Relations, has Combatted Communism in Latin America, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
    By Edmund S. Whitman. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Threefold Way to Western Hemisphere Unity: Investment, Interdependence, Participation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 11: United Fruit Company Annual Report for the Year 1957, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 12: U.F. Report, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 13: U.F. Report, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 14: Shareholder, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Item 15: How an American Company, Through Advertising and Public Relations, has Combatted Communism in Latin America, Publication (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Box: 64, folder: 20 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Retirement and Death Benefit Plan for Employees of United Fruit Company and Participating Subsidiary Companies: Twenty-Fourth Annual Report of the Administrative Committee, Publication (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Alimentos Futuros de las Americas, Publication (Box 64, Folder 20)
    By James Rorty. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 21 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Organization Development Plan, Publication (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: United Fruit's Experiment in International Partnership, Publication (Box 64, Folder 21)
    By Paul Deutschman. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: United Fruit Company, Publication (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Box: 64, folder: 22 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: United Gas Log, Publication (Box 64, Folder 22)
    June 1953. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 23 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Functions of Board of Directors and Management Staff and Company Organization Charts, Publication (Box 64, Folder 23)
    September 1, 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 24 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: 1965 Report to Employees, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: The United Gas Improvement Company: 84th Annual Report 1965, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: News Bulletin, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
    Sept.-Oct. 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Administrative Guide for Employee Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
    September 15, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Mestanews, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
    September-October 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: UGI Corporation 1971 Annual Report, Publication (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Box: 64, folder: 25 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Position Description Form, Publication (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Position Description Form, Publication (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Clerical Job Description Form, Publication (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: Clerical Job Description Form, Publication (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Employees Handbook, Publication (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Box: 64, folder: 26 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The United Housing Foundation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: United Housing Foundation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: What Every Cooperator Should Know: A Guide to Cooperative Hours, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: What Every Cooperator Should Know: A Guide to Cooperative Hours, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Now You Can Buy An Apartment For As Little As $49 per Month after a down payment, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: East River Housing Corporation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Site Plan: Queensview North, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: Morningside Gardens, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
    Bulletin No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Housing and Gardens, Too, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
    By Abraham E. Kazan. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Queensview, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
    By Louis H. Pink. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Now You Can Buy an Apartment for as Little as $49 per Month after down payment, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 12: Facts About Queensview West: A Non-Profit Cooperative Housing Development, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 13: A Housing Development Cooperatively Built and Operated, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 14: Steps to Cooperative Housing, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 15: United Housing Foundation: Cooperative Housing Press Service, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 16: The Story of Amalgamated Warbasse Houses, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 17: We've Come of Age, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Item 18: 30 Years of Amalgamated Cooperative Housing, Publication (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Box: 64, folder: 27 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Co-Op Contract, Publication (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: United Housing Foundation Annual Report, Publication (Box 64, Folder 27)
    September 1955. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 28 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography: Workshop Seminars and Short Courses, Publication (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: Manager-Employee Relations, Publication (Box 64, Folder 28)
- Box: 64, folder: 29 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The United Nations Development Decage: Proposals for Action, Publication (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Helping Economic Development in Asia and the Far East: The Work Ecafe, Publication (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: United Nations Economic and Social Council, Publication (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: The Expanded Programme of Technical Assistance, Publication (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Conference on Productivity, Publication (Box 64, Folder 29)
    February 11, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 30 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: The New AOA Administration on Aging, Publication (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Box: 64, folder: 31 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The AID Story, Publication (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Item 2: Alliance for Prgoressan American Partnership, Publication (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Box: 64, folder: 32 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Employee-Management Cooperation in ASCS, Publication (Box 64, Folder 32)
    May 1965. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 33 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: An Introduction to USMC Research, Publication (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: United States Military Footwear, Publication (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Box: 64, folder: 34 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Efficiency Through Hygiene, Publication (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: "How to Study for the People's Welfare", Publication (Box 64, Folder 34)
    By John F. O'Connell. Item is in English.
- Box: 64, folder: 35 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: AMC Organizational Directory Chart, Publication (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: HQ AMC Organizational Objectives and Concept of Staff Operation, Publication (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Box: 64, folder: 36 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policy, Publication (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: AEC Contract Policy and Operations, Publication (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: U.S. Atomic Energy Commission AEC Manual, Publication (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: United States Atomic Energy Commission: Opportunities for Challenging Careers, Publication (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: A Careerin the United States Atomic Energy Commission, Publication (Box 64, Folder 36)